

const spanelstina = {
  
  name: 'Španělština',
  ttsLang: 'es-ES',
  lessons: [
    
    {
      title: 'Lekce 1',
      pdf: '',
      image: '',
      
      questions: [
        {
         question: 'Dobrý den',
          answer: 'Buenos días',
        },
        {
         question: 'Pepík',
          answer: 'Pepe',
        },
        {
         question: 'Marie',
          answer: 'María',
        },
        {
         question: 'Jan',
          answer: 'Juan',
        },
        {
         question: 'Josef',
          answer: 'José',
        },
        {
         question: 'Já',
          answer: 'Yo',
        },
        {
         question: 'A',
          answer: 'Y',
        },
        {
         question: 'Víno (m)',
          answer: 'Vino',
        },
        {
         question: 'Ty',
          answer: 'Tú',
        },
        {
         question: 'Práce (m)',
          answer: 'Trabajo',
        },
        {
         question: 'Čas (m)',
          answer: 'Tiempo',
        },
        {
         question: 'Je mi zima.',
         answer: 'Tengo frío.',
        },
        {
         question: 'Je mi horko.',
         answer: 'Tengo calor.',
        },
        {
         question: 'Má (on, ona, ono)',
         answer: 'Tiene',
        },
        {
         question: 'Máš (ty)',
         answer: 'Tienes',
        },
        {
         question: 'Mám (já)',
         answer: 'Tengo',
        },
        {
         question: 'Mít',
         answer: 'Tener',
        },
        {
         question: 'Telefon (m)',
         answer: 'Teléfono',
        },
        {
         question: 'Čaj (m)',
         answer: 'Té',
        },
        {
         question: 'Odpoledne (ž)',
         answer: 'Tarde',
        },
        {
         question: 'Také',
         answer: 'También',
        },
        {
         question: 'Ano',
         answer: 'Sí',
        },
        {
         question: 'Slečna (ž)',
         answer: 'Señorita',
        },
        {
         question: 'Paní (ž)',
         answer: 'Señora',
        },
        {
         question: 'Pán (m)',
         answer: 'Señor',
        },
        {
         question: 'Žízeň (m)',
         answer: 'Sed',
        },
        {
         question: 'Na zdraví',
         answer: 'Salud',
        },
        {
         question: 'Zdraví (ž)',
         answer: 'Salud',
        },
        {
         question: 'Chleba (m)',
         answer: 'Pan',
        },
        {
         question: 'Večer, noc (m)',
         answer: 'Noche',
        },
        {
         question: 'Ne',
         answer: 'No',
        },
        {
         question: 'Není zač',
         answer: 'De nada',
        },
        {
         question: 'Nic',
         answer: 'Nada',
        },
        {
         question: 'Velmi',
         answer: 'Muy',
        },
        {
         question: 'Ahoj',
         answer: 'Hola',
        },
        {
         question: 'Díky',
         answer: 'Gracias',
        },
        {
         question: 'Chladno (m)',
         answer: 'Frío',
        },
        {
         question: 'Zima (m)',
         answer: 'Frío',
        },
        {
         question: 'Studený/á',
         answer: 'Frío/Fría',
        },
        {
         question: 'Ona',
         answer: 'Ella',
        },
        {
         question: 'On',
         answer: 'Él',
        },
        {
         question: 'Peníze (m)',
         answer: 'Dinero',
        },
        {
         question: 'Den',
         answer: 'Día',
        },
        {
         question: 'Čokoláda (m)',
         answer: 'Chocolate',
        },
        {
         question: 'Teplo (m)',
         answer: 'Calor',
        },
        {
         question: 'Káva (m)',
         answer: 'Café',
        },
        {
         question: 'Kakao (m)',
         answer: 'Cacao',
        },
        {
         question: 'Dobrý/á',
         answer: 'Bueno/Buena',
        },
        {
         question: 'Sbohem (ahoj)',
         answer: 'Adiós',
        },
      ],
    },



  ],
}

export default spanelstina
